This next position is often referred to as alligator.
We're going to be moving down to our back.
So, from a seated position, you're just going to swing your legs over and we're going to gently, one leg at a time, lie yourself down and you can place your hands, under your leg, if you'd like.
Just rolling all the way down, nice and gently.
We're going to take the arms out, to your side, palms up, perpendicular to your body.
Both legs are going to come up, toward the ceiling, and we're going to take a deep breath.
Inhale and as you exhale, slowly taking both legs over to the right and if you'd like to help keep the left shoulder on the floor, you can look to the left side or else you can just keep your head to the center.
Just taking deep breaths as you hold this pose, trying to keep your feet close to your hand or wrist.
Inhaling, exhaling and trying to press that left hip, close to the floor and then you're going to use your breath and your obliques, exhale slowly, bring both legs back to center.
Then repeat the same thing on the other side.
Deep breath in and exhale, both legs go slowly over to the left side, keeping the right hip on the floor.
You can look to the right side, if it helps you keep the right shoulder on the floor.
Inhale, just exhale, relax.
Deep breath in and exhale and again, using your breath and your obliques and you can use the opposite hand to assist, bringing both legs back to center.
And that's your alligator.
You can bring the knees into the chest, wrapping your hands around your legs.
Just relax and loosen the spine and feel the effects of the pose.